http://www.littlekickers.co.uk/privacy.aspx

South Africa
Spain (en)
Spain (es)
Switzerland
Thailand
Turkey
Menu
Find a classCoaching OpportunitiesFranchise OpportunitiesAbout usShop
Birthday PartiesNurseriesJobsTestimonialsLatest News
sitemapprivacy policycookie policyterms & conditions
Privacy policy At Little Kickers Holdings Limited, we take your privacy seriously and this privacy statement explains what personal data or information we collect from you and from people who visit our website and how we use it. If you have any questions regarding this statement and our privacy practices, please contact us by email info@littlekickers.co.uk or by post at Little Kickers Franchises Limited, Blewbury Ranch, Bessels Way, Blewbury, Oxon, OX11 9NH.   Who are we?Little Kickers is a company registered in England, number 5153525.  Our registered office address is c/o Tenon, Springpark House, Basing View, Basingstoke, Hampshire, RG21 4HG. For the purposes of Data Protection Little Kickers is a data controller. Our ICO registration number is: Z1211801. What personal data or information do we collect?The personal information we collect may include your name, address, email address, IP address and information regarding what pages you access on this website and when. How do we collect data or information from you?We collect data or information about you when you use our website, or when you make an enquiry about our products or services, enquire about a job or franchise opportunity, or if you register to be sent an email news update.  How is your information used?We collect your personal data or information to operate our business effectively and provide you with the best information on our products and services. We may use your information to: ·     To carry out our obligations arising from any contract or contract negotiations entered into
by you or us as a customer or prospective customer.·      Process an enquiry that you have made to us.·      Process your order and process after sales service·     To contact you to discuss franchise opportunities or products and services that we believe
may be of interest to you.·      To process a job application.·      Send you communications that you have requested, for example our email newsletter. ·      Maintain a class register.  We believe that all these purposes are justified on the basis of our legitimate interests in running and promoting the Little Kickers classes, our contractual requirements to deliver the agreed franchise to you, and our legal obligations, both as a Franchisor and responsible employer.  If you would like to know more, please read below: Details of our processing 1. Prospective Customers Type of Data Held·      Name and contact information·      Information and documents relating to the services we are providing, including communications
with you. Length of Time HeldWe will retain information about you for the duration of the enquiry, then a further 5 years. How Data is HeldData is stored in secure servers in both the EEA and non-EEA (Canada) servers. 2. Customers Type of Data Held ·      Parent Name and contact information·      Name and Date of Birth of child·      Information and documents relating to the services we are providing, including communications
with you.·      Billing and payment information (NB: we do not store Credit or Debit Card details). Length of Time HeldWe will retain information about you for the duration of our contractual relationship with you, then for an additional 4 years. We retain financial transaction records for 6 years, following the end of the current financial year. How Data is HeldData is stored in secure servers in both the EEA and non-EEA (Canada) servers. Transaction details are stored in PayPal, CyberSource and World Pay servers, which may be outside the EEA. 3. Job Applicants Type of Data Held·      Name and contact information·      CV and application form.·      Interview notes (for those short-listed) Length of Time HeldWe will retain information about you for the duration of the recruitment campaign, then one year. How Data is HeldData is stored in secure servers in both the EEA and non-EEA (Canada) servers. 4. Current and Former Employees Type of Data Held·      Name, date of birth, and contact information·      National insurance number and Unique Tax Reference (UTR)·      Information relating to your qualifications and experience·      Information relating to performance reviews. Length of Time HeldWe will retain information about you for the duration of our contractual relationship with you, then for an additional 3 years.   How Data is HeldData is stored on secure EEA-based servers. 5. Prospective Franchisees and Franchisees  Type of Data Held·      Contact details·      Date of Birth and Gender·      Spousal information·      Income, assets and net worth·      Personality Test Length of Time HeldSuccessful franchisees personal information is retained for the duration of the franchise agreement then a further 4 years. Unsuccessful franchisee applications are retained for a maximum of 12-months How Data is HeldData is stored in secure servers in both the EEA and non-EEA (Canada) servers. Who has access to your information? We do not sell or rent your personal data or information to any third party or share your information with third parties for their marketing purposes.   We will disclose your data or information if required by law, for example by a court order or for the prevention of fraud or other crime.                                                       We may pass your information on to our third-party service providers, agents or subcontractors (e.g. NetGuides and Spark Growth) for the purposes of completing a task or providing services to you on our behalf.  However, we disclose only the personal information necessary to deliver that service and have a contract in place that requires them to keep your information secure and not to use it for their own marketing purposes.   Third party services providers who act as data processors on our behalf:  NetGuides provide IT system and website services to Little Kickers. They cannot use the data we hold for their own purposes, you can read their privacy policy here.Spark Growth provide digital marketing strategy services to Little Kickers.  They cannot use the data we hold for their own purposes, you can read their privacy policy here.SkyPrep provide Little Kickers with an online training platform for use by Franchisees.  They cannot use the data we hold for their own purposes, you can read their privacy policy here.SalesForce provide IT administration system  services to Little Kickers. They cannot use the data we hold for their own purposes, you can read their privacy policy here.PayPal provide payment processor and acquirer services to Little Kickers. They cannot use the data we hold for their own purposes, you can read their privacy policy here.WorldPay provide payment processor services to Little Kickers. They cannot use the data we hold for their own purposes, you can read their privacy policy here.Cybersource provide payment gateway services to Little Kickers. They cannot use the data we hold for their own purposes, you can read their privacy policy here.Franchise Supermarket provide franchise brokerage services to Little Kickers. They cannot use data we hold for their own purposes, you can read their privacy policy here.  Transfers outside of the European Economic AreaPersonal information in the European Union is protected by data protection laws but other countries do not necessarily protect your personal information in the same way.  The European Economic Area (EEA) covers all countries in the EU plus, Norway, Liechtenstein and Iceland.  Some of the third-party providers we use to help us manage our business and services may involve data transferring to the Canada or other countries outside of the EEA, for example PayPal, World Pay, Sky Prep and Spark Growth. Your Choices & RightsWe understand that you trust us with your personal information and we are committed to ensuring you can manage the privacy and security of your personal information yourself. With respect to the information relating to you that ends up in our possession, and recognising that it is your choice to provide us with your personally identifiable information, we commit to giving you the ability to do all of the following: You can verify the details you have submitted to Little Kickers by contacting us by email: info@littlekickers.co.uk or phone 01235 859 250.  Our security procedures mean that we may request proof of identity before we reveal information, including your e-mail address and possibly your address.You can always feel free to update us on your details at any point by sending an email to info@littlekickers.co.ukYou can unsubscribe from receiving marketing emails from us by clicking the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any email. Once you do this, you will no longer receive any emails from us. You can request a readable copy of the personal data we hold on you at any time. To do this, please contact us via email info@littlekickers.co.uk You also have the right to lodge a complaint about our processing with the UK’s Information Commissioner’s Office (hyperlink https://ico.org.uk/).    Keeping your data secureWhen you give us personal information we take steps to ensure that it’s treated securely and strive to protect it on our internal systems.   Emailing usWe use Transport Layer Security (TLS) to encrypt and protect email traffic in line with government standards. If your email service does not support TLS, you should be aware that any emails we send or receive may not be protected in transit. We will also monitor any emails sent to us, including file attachments, for viruses or malicious software. Please be aware that you have a responsibility to ensure that any email you send is within the bounds of the law. Changes to this privacy noticeWe keep our privacy notice under regular review. This privacy notice was last updated on 11/02/2019.
Birthday PartiesNurseriesJobsTestimonialsLatest News
Menu
Menu
United Kingdom
Australia
Brazil
Canada
Chile
Spain (en)
Spain (es)
